export const Question =[
    //1
    {
        question:"< What is React />",
        optionA:" Big Library",
        optionB:"Framework",
        optionC:"i dont know",
        optionD:"Small Libarary part of Vue",
        answer:"A"
    },
    //2
    {
        question:"< What is Jsx in React />",
        optionA:"It is framewrok of Css",
        optionB:" Element ",
        optionC:"It is similiar to Html runs in React",
        optionD:" Part of styled Components",
        answer:""
    },
      //3
      {
        question:"< What is Virtual Dom />",
        optionA:"Updates the JSX if element updates.",
        optionB:" It updates faster and no memory wastage ",
        optionC:" DOM manipulation is very easy.",
        optionD:" All is true  ",
        answer:"D"
    },
      //4
      {
        question:"< What are the features of React ( Find incorrect) />",
        optionA:"It uses server side-rendering",
        optionB:"It uses Virtual Dom ",
        optionC:" It doesnt follow uni-directional data flow ",
        optionD:"Using React, writing UI test cases become easy",
        answer:"C"
    },
      //5
      {
        question:"< Find solution const {state , setState}= useState() />",
        optionA:"const [state , setState] = useState(}",
        optionB:" const [setState, state] = useState()",
        optionC:"const [state , setState] = useState()",
        optionD:"const {useState}= React",
        answer:"C"
    },
      //6
      {
        question:"< All imports must be ..? />",
        optionA:"Top",
        optionB:"Bottom",
        optionC:"Middle ",
        optionD:" Where you would use ",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //7
      {
        question:"< What company created React />",
        optionA:" Microsoft  ",
        optionB:" Facebook",
        optionC:"Instagram ",
        optionD:"Telegram",
        answer:"B"
    },
      //8
      {
        question:"< You can use useReducer instead of ..? />",
        optionA:"useState",
        optionB:"useRef",
        optionC:"useCallback",
        optionD:"All of this",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //9
      {
        question:"< How many hooks has React />",
        optionA:"9",
        optionB:"17",
        optionC:"14",
        optionD:"8",
        answer:"C"
    },
      //10
      {
        question:"< What is state ? />",
        optionA:"It  is function that changes(any many options) your variable",
        optionB:"Smth makes your code safety in react",
        optionC:"It is a Virtual Dom",
        optionD:"it is == Styled Components",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //11
      {
        question:"< What is state management in React ?/>",
        optionA:"You can use it to pass states through components",
        optionB:"I dont know but i use it ",
        optionC:"Second name of state",
        optionD:"React doesn`t use it ",
        answer:""
    },
      //12
      {
        question:"< What is Components ?  />",    
        optionA:"It is file inside of src file that comes with react",
        optionB:"Files to help clean coding ",
        optionC:"Components describe any composable behavior, and this includes rendering, lifecycle, and state.",
        optionD:"Unneccary Files ",
        answer:"C"
    },
      //13
      {
        question:"< What is Props ? />",
        optionA:"Props is arguments that passes through Components",
        optionB: " Arguments ",
        optionC:"It helps to run your code faster ",
        optionD:"It is type of React extension",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //14
    {
        question:"< What is useEffect Hook ? />",
        optionA:"It is simiiar to useCallback hook",
        optionB:"Same with useLayoutEffect hook",
        optionC:"The useEffect Hook is used for fetching data,directly updating the DOM, and timers in your components.",
        optionD:"We can use it to fetch data",
        answer:"C"
    },
      //15
      {
        question:"< React hooks ? />",
        optionA:"Hooks allow function components to have access to state and other React features",
        optionB:"It is another name of Components",
        optionC:"File name ",
        optionD:"I dont know ",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //16
      {
        question:"< About useRef hook />",
        optionA:"It makes your styling easier ",
        optionB:"It is logic operator",
        optionC:"You can use it to create own hook",
        optionD:"The useRef Hook allows you to persist values between renders.",
        answer:"D"
    },
      //17
      {
        question:"< Which is right (const [name , setName] = useState('')/>",
        optionA:"<input onChange={()=>setName(e.target.value)}",
        optionB:"<input onChange={(e)=>setName(e.target.value)}",
        optionC:"<input onChange={(e)=>name(e.target.value)}",
        optionD:"<input onChange={()=>setName(target.value)}",
        answer:"B"
    },
      //18
      {
        question:"< What is Custom Hook />",
        optionA:"It is used to create your own hook",
        optionB:"it is used to change your state",
        optionC:"It is used to create own state",
        optionD:"It is used to make components",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //19
      {
        question:"< Find correct part(useEffect)  />",
        optionA:"useEffect(()=>{})",
        optionB:"usEffect(()=>{}",
        optionC:"useEffect()=>{}",
        optionD:"B and C ",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //20
      {
        question:"< Find correct answer(Map)  />",
        optionA:"smth.map((arr, key)=>{<key={key}> {arr} </> }",
        optionB:"smth.map((key)=>{<>key</>",
        optionC:"smth.map(()=> smth ",
        optionD:"All is true",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //21
      {
        question:"< We use ... method to display array />",
        optionA:"Filter",
        optionB:"Map",
        optionC:"Reduce",
        optionD:"All ",
        answer:"D"
    },
      //22
      {
        question:"< Inline Styling in react />",
        optionA:"< div style={{color:red}}>",
        optionB:"< div style={{color:`red`}}>",
        optionC:"< div style={{color=red}}>",
        optionD:"< div style={{color=`red`}}>",
        answer:"B"
    },
      //23
      {
        question:"< About useContext Hook ? />",
        optionA:"It is a good way to use state inside of any Component",
        optionB:"It is another name of props ",
        optionC:"B and A",
        optionD:"All is true ",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //24
      {
        question:"< useContext usage is ..? />",
        optionA:"const {state , setState} = useContext(nameOfContext)",
        optionB:"const [state, setState ] = nameOfContext",
        optionC:"const [ state , setState ] = createContext()",
        optionD:"const [ state , setState ] = useContext()",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //25
      {
        question:"<How to give a class or id in React />  ",
        optionA:" class , idName ",
        optionB:" className , idName ",
        optionC:"className , id ",
        optionD:"claSS , iD",
        answer:"C"
    },
      //26
      {
        question:"< Hooks or function should be written ..? />",
        optionA:"Above of the  Component ",
        optionB:"Middle ",
        optionC:"After `import` ",
        optionD:"Above of return ()",
        answer:"D"
    },
      //27
      {
        question:"< Define error <div className=``> <div> />",
        optionA:"Missing /",
        optionB:"Error of giving class",
        optionC:"ClassName is valid here Give it id ",
        optionD:"there is no error",
        answer:"A"
    },
      //28
      {
        question:"< React is built by ..? (programming language) />",
        optionA:"Python",
        optionB:"Java",
        optionC:" Java Script",
        optionD:"Php",
        answer:"C"
    },
      //29
      {
        question:"< React runs ...? />",
        optionA:"Directly runs ",
        optionB:"First it runs in Html(in public folder )  and goes to src file ",
        optionC:"B and A true ",
        optionD:"All is true",
        answer:"B"
    },
      //30
      {
        question:"< Find error const App = () => {} />",
        optionA:"Missing /",
        optionB:"Missing `` ",
        optionC:"There  is no incorrect",
        optionD:"const is unavilable use `var` ",
        answer:"C"
    }
]

